♪ In the not too
distant future ♪
♪ Way down in Deep 13 ♪
♪ The evil Dr. Forrester ♪
♪ Was hatching a nasty scheme ♪
♪ He hired a temp by
the name of Mike ♪
♪ Just a regular
Joe he didn't like ♪
♪ His experiment needed
a good test case ♪
♪ So he conked him
on the noggin' ♪
♪ And he shot him into space ♪
♪ Get me down ♪
♪ I'll send him cheesy movies ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ The worst I can find ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ And we'll monitor his mind ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Now keep in mind
Mike can't control ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ When the movies begin or end ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ He'll try to keep his sanity ♪
♪ With the help of
his robot friends ♪
♪ (Chainsaw whirring) ♪
♪ Robot roll call ♪
♪ Cambot ♪
♪ Show yourself ♪
♪ Gypsy ♪
♪ I'm not ready ♪
♪ Tom Servo ♪
♪ Hello there ♪
♪ Croooow! ♪
♪ That's one O ♪
♪ If you're wondering how
he eats and breathes ♪
♪ And other science facts ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Just repeat to yourself
it's just a show ♪
♪ I should really just relax ♪
♪ Did I tell you
my mother's here? ♪
♪ For Mystery Science Theater ♪
♪ 3000 ♪
♪ (strumming of guitar) ♪
(slamming shut)
(whizzing down)
(thudding shut)
(whizzing shut)
(clicking shut)
- Hi everyone, I'm Mike.
Welcome back.
I'm just waiting around
for Tom, Crow and then--
- Hi Mike.
Mike, Tom and I are
taking a very active role
in our personal security.
- Yep, that's why we
got these taser guns.
- Mm-hmm.
- Hey, you know, you wanna
be careful with those things.
Auugh!
- Mike, you're scaring him!
Don't hurt him, Mike!
Geez, wow, I've never
seen him like that.
- I know, I know, I
didn't wanna shoot him
but he scared me.
He stirs!
Hit him with your
peppercorn Mace.
- Careful with that!
Aaahhh!
- Stand down, you're
scaring me, Mike!
Mike, don't Mike!
Okay, okay get your
green dye so we can
permanently mark
the perpetrator.
- Oh right.
- He's scaring me again.
- We'll be right back.
- Mike, Mike don't!
- Ahhhhh!
(upbeat music)
- Guys, this isn't funny,
my face is really green!
- Ha ha ha ha ha.
- It's not that green, Mike.
- It's incredibly green.
Does this stuff even
come off anyway?
- It's just a little--
- Really Mike, it's
not that green.
- No it's not.
- And now Dr. F is calling.
(robots laugh)
My face is green.
- Surprise, it's me.
My Clayton has asked me
to invite all of you.
Clayton!
To a little recital
I suggested he give.
Clayton!
- Hi guys.
I presume you remember Mother.
She's going to be
visiting here for a while.
- Living.
- Living, living her for
an interminable amount,
indeterminate amount
of time and it's really
great to have her here.
Anyway, I used to play the
trombone and Mom thought
it would be good if you heard.
- Nobody wants to hear
you talk, Clayton.
- Ah, right.
Here.
(pages flipping)
(tapping out tempo)
(amateurish trombone music)
(ruler striking metal)
- Flat!
(trombone playing)
(ruler striking metal)
Flat!
- I know!
(ruler striking metal)
- Sharp!
No, flat!
(trombone music deteriorates)
(ruler striking metal)
Flat!
- Oh, well that's not bad.
Not bad at all but
maybe if you tried
something a little
more like this.
(skillful trombone music)
- Whoa!
Whoa.
Oh yeah.
(skillful trombone music)
Yeah.
- Bring it back.
- Oh, sing to me.
- See, Clayton, if
you practiced, you
could be like Art.
- Oh, Mother.
- Don't give me that.
You do the thing
with the tongue.
(trombone blaring)
Oh, Clayton, you
are so embarrassing.
Everyone is better than you.
What do I have to do
to get you to act like
a member of the human race?
Oh, if I'd only had the daughter
I'd prayed for instead of you.
(trombone blaring)
Amateur!
Oh Clayton Deborah Susan
Forrester, you've ruined
it for me again.
Why does this
always happen to me?
- I trust you'll
put up with Mother.
She's really a dear, dear--
(items clattering to floor,
mother muttering to self)
Anyway, your movie this week
is "Night of the Blood Beast."
There's a short as well.
- I have no son.
I have no son.
- I do love her.
She's a beauty.
- I never let his
father touch me.
♪ Hold that tiger ♪
♪ Hold the tiger ♪
♪ Here kitty, kitty,
kitty, kitty, kitty ♪
- We got movie time!
(alarms blaring, shouting)
(doors whizzing
open in sequence)
(final door creaking open)
- [Tom] Wow, how many
times Michael Jackson
and Lisa Marie had sex!
(all chuckle)
- [Mike] Oh, I was
known as something
of a chick handler myself.
- [Tom] Pretty crowded
honeymoon, huh?
What with all the names.
♪ It's spring time for Hitler ♪
♪ And Germany, duh duh duh duh ♪
- [Mike] Oh, he directs
the best honeymoons.
- Lucy, I'm dead!
- [Movie Narrator] Once upon
a time or maybe it should
be twice upon a time because
this story begins where
most stories end, there was bit
of excitement up on Cloud Seven.
On this particular
morning, the head angel
had called a conference to
talk about Jeff and Mary
and their guardian
angel, Wilbur, was late.
- Where is Wilbur?
- Wilbur.
- I'll send every cherub in
the place off to look for him.
- Dah!
- Hiya, fellas!
Let's get this show on the road.
- It's already on the road.
- I'm sorry, chief.
We've got so many new
clients we'll have
to open a new branch office.
- These clients are
your immediate concern
if you want to
keep your license.
- Oh, yes sir, yes sir.
Yes sir, chief.
- [Tom] Poor Buck Henry.
- Marriages are made in heaven
but there's follow up work too.
- [Tom] You want I should
show her a good time?
- Jeff and Mary have
been married for a year
and they haven't had
a real honeymoon yet.
(vocalizing like
a wah-wah pedal)
- Well, everything's under
control; they're starting
on their honeymoon today.
- That's what they think too.
But they're going to
find out differently.
- [Tom] Gasp!
- Unless you get
down there right away
and take care of things.
- [Tom] I want them eliminated.
- Something's come up?
- Something is coming up
in exactly 30 seconds.
(one of the riffers
pretends to gag)
Now get going.
- Yes sir, chief!
Geronimo!
- Just go ya big poof.
(one of the riffers
pretends to vomit)
- Wilbur!
Oh Wilbur!
- [Tom] Dear God I
hate theater people.
- [Mike] Sir, should
we get on to wars
or starvation or anything?
- Oh, Mrs. Muir, oh ho ho ho ho!
- [Tom] I love it when I
get a call in my pants.
- [Mike] Just answer
my hair dryer here.
- Hey, chief?
- Wilbur, make
yourself invisible.
- Oh I almost forgot.
- Hah, he's trying to
have a Montclair moment.
Ha ha ha ha!
(vocalizes plane
crashing sound effect)
(dramatic music)
- Bzzt-bzzt!
(Tom screams in pain)
- [Tom] Hey, now they'll
get immaculate reception.
(laughs) Sorry.
- [Mike] You know, I
had an angel rottin'
in my chimney once.
- [Tom] Yuck.
- [Mike] Sad.
- I'm sorry, chief.
I've got to get organized.
Besides, no one
can see me up here.
Yes sir.
- There he is, officer!
- [Tom] Come down off the roof.
- Ah ha, look!
There's a frisbee in the gutter.
- [Tom] Oh no, angel dust!
That's a rattlesnake.
- [Mike] They live
in a doll house.
- You know, they should fire
grandma as their decorator.
- [Tom] I'm leaving you.
- [Mike] Oh, I thought
I was leaving you.
- Have you got everything?
- Everything, including you.
- [Mike] Oh, so hot.
- Well, let's go then.
(phone ringing)
- [Mike] Eugh, it's the Pope
about the one sexual position.
- They're on to us.
- Hello?
- [Gordon] Jeff, this is Gordon.
- Oh hello, Gordon.
And goodbye Gordon, Mary
and I are just leaving.
- Now wait a minute!
Something's come up.
- It can't come up.
When I finished the
score for the show,
you said I could take
Mary on our honeymoon.
We've waited a year
now and we're going.
- Now hold on, Jeff, it's Sonya.
Our wishing number.
The wardrobe came
and she doesn't care
much about the music.
If we don't have a new
tune by tomorrow morning,
she's not gonna
sign for the show.
- Look Gordon, rehearsals
don't start for four weeks yet.
- [Tom] I haven't
had it in years.
- We're on our honeymoon.
- Now listen Jeff.
- E.G. Marshall is here.
- If you don't come up
with that new music,
there won't be any show and
there won't be any honeymoon.
Now you can write a
new melody in 24 hours.
There's no problem at all.
You must have at least a
dozen old tunes lying around.
(phone clicking into receiver)
(vocalizes cartoonish
shocked noise)
- The wishing song?
- [Mike] I wanna have sex.
- No problem at all.
- And me completely out of blow.
- [Tom] S'cuse me while
I light my spliff.
- [Mike] What would Liberace do?
Ah, I better not do that.
- [Tom] One of 32 short
films about this guy.
- Ah let's see, what
rhymes with blue balls?
- [Mike] Wait a minute!
I work for Otis Elevators;
I don't write music!
- [Mike] Ah, Mickey
Rourke came over to help.
- No inspiration, darling?
- I couldn't write "The
Farmer in the Dell" today.
- Why would you wanna write him?
- That temperamental
ballerina is like--
- Take it easy.
Look, it's way past dinnertime
and you haven't eaten lunch yet.
- [Tom] Well, I had three packs.
- I'm not hungry.
- I'll fix some coffee.
- [Tom] I'll give this to the
man in the kitchen. (humming)
(phone ringing)
- Oh, another one of your
scores has fallen apart.
(piano music)
- Yes?
- [Sonya] Hello, Mary?
- [Tom] Vhat are vou vearing?
- Yes, Sonya?
- You tell Jeffrey the dear
boy that I love his words
but I want more wishing
in the wishing song.
- You're absolutely right.
He couldn't agree with you more.
He's working on it right now.
It's almost finished.
- So shut up.
- Goodbye.
- [Mike] Copper bottom bitch.
Another sandwich, dear?
- [Tom] If I pull hard enough
I can snap my head off.
(strained grunting)
♪ I wish I had a
castle in the sky ♪
- [Mike] Well, wish in one hand
and crap in the other and
see which piles up first.
♪ Oh way up high where
bluebirds like to fly ♪
♪ I wish I could have
sex with Louis Nye ♪
(discordant piano keys)
♪ A cozy little castle
with a 100 rooms or more ♪
♪ I wouldn't have to
dress like Tipper Gore ♪
♪ With stars for windows,
clouds for rugs ♪
♪ A rainbow for a door ♪
- [Tom] Phwooosh!
♪ I wish ♪
- [Mike] Honey, I'm
trying to compose in here
if you could keep it down.
- I just wish I had
a decent kitchen.
- Hah, angels work about
as hard as road crews.
- [Tom] A little
pecorino. (giggling)
Poppies.
♪ I wish the faucet
wouldn't drip all day ♪
- Aim high, sister!
- [Tom] Oh, I wish Hardware
Hank hadn't done my kitchen!
♪ I wish that
refrigerator door ♪
♪ Would close and say closed ♪
- [Mike] Oh sure everyone
dump on the refrigerator.
Fine, I'll close.
- Miss Betty Furness and
the new Westinghouse.
♪ I wish I had a stove ♪
♪ Whose pilot light
was always lit ♪
- Well, don't look for it now.
It's only available
in the year 2000.
♪ Furthermore, a
kitchen phone at hand ♪
♪ When friends call
up to chat a bit ♪
(riffers vocalizing
along to song)
(phone ringing)
♪ Hello, yes, it is
Mary, how are you? ♪
♪ Fine? ♪
♪ They say your kitchen
dazzles every eye ♪
♪ A brand-new sink,
a built-in oven ♪
- [Garbled Voice] Mary,
this is important.
♪ A new refrigerator
and a phone ♪
- [Garbled Voice]
Get out of the house,
it's a terrible accident.
♪ A kitchen phone ♪
- [Garbled Voice] Gotta
get to the hospital.
♪ Gotta go, goodbye,
goodbye, goodbye ♪
- [Garbled Voice] There's
blood on everything.
The nuclear reactor exploded.
♪ I'll call you later ♪
♪ It's all part of
my kitchen fantasy ♪
(upbeat music)
(string music)
- [Tom] No, no.
- Have some bear
gall juice, honey.
♪ I wish my living
room were all redone ♪
♪ I think owning a
newspaper would be fun ♪
♪ New drapes, new
rugs, oh this is fun ♪
- [Tom] My God honey, what
have you done to our lives!
♪ It's nice to
have a telephone ♪
♪ To blend with my
new drapes and rug ♪
♪ A living room
that's all our own. ♪
- [Tom] Bang, bang, bang,
bang, bang bang bang!
- [Mike] Honey, I can't
stop smiling, I'm in Hell.
- Ah, bubby and sissy,
aren't they wonderful?
- [Tom] This might
actually be sex right here.
- [Mike] Okay, where
can I put ya honey?
- [Tom] I wrote this
one for Scott Thorson.
- [Mike] Meanwhile
soldiers are dying
in the mud in North Korea.
- Ah, who cares?
That's her come whither look.
♪ The bedroom should be
changed completely too ♪
- [Tom] Ah, hang a
parachute, put up
the beer can collection.
♪ Perhaps a color
scheme of golden blue ♪
- [Mike] That's about
as sexy as a garage.
♪ New furniture
and lots of room ♪
♪ For all my clothes ♪
(riffers vocalizing
horse clip-clopping)
(riffers exclaim)
♪ On second thought, I
might try dusty rose ♪
- One bed's for them; the
other one's for little grandma.
- [Tom] Jeff and I were
gonna get the racing car beds
but we decided on these.
♪ A lady likes to
have a chance ♪
♪ To change her mind ♪
- [Mike] No no no
no, none of that.
♪ Like a yellow room with
turquoise and white ♪
♪ And maybe a telephone
that lights up at night ♪
♪ I wish I may, I wish I-- ♪
- Might.
♪ Might ♪
- [Tom] Ah, sort of a
Western-y, gingham-y,
Oriental Danish
modern-esque Prairie School
sort of thing, huh?
(telephone ringing)
- [Mike] Pills, pills, pills,
pills, where are the pills?
(chuckling)
We gotta get outta
here, I smell gas!
(phone ringing)
- Hello?
Hello?
They hung up.
- Here's how far
I've gotten, Law.
- It's probably Gordon
sitting there like a vulture.
(discordant piano hit)
Call him back!
Maybe I'll have it in a
day or two but not tonight.
I haven't gotten one idea
left to rub against another.
- [Tom] Don't say rub or grind
or moist or hard or gristle.
- His line is busy.
- Well, try it again.
If he and Sonya can't wait,
I don't care what they do.
- [Mike] Get away from me!
- Honey, is that a gay
man on the Johnsons' roof?
- [Tom] Should we get a gay
man for our roof, honey?
- Why don't we call him later?
- No, now!
- All right.
- [Mike] I am your
damn secretary, fine.
- Honey, your cocaine
is all over the phone.
(spinning of dial)
(riffers vocalizing Pink
Floyd's song "Money")
(busy tone)
(phone clicking onto receiver)
- Wait a minute, do that again.
(dial spinning)
- [Mike] Okay, now
rustle your skirt,
flap your arms and
run the vacuum.
(dial spinning)
- Yeah, yeah!
Why not?
- [Mike] I'll call
someone to write the song.
- Again, do it again!
(dial spinning in
tune with piano music)
♪ Everybody was kung-fu
fighting, yeah ♪
- It works!
- Sure, for a tuneless
sort of thing.
- [Tom] Don't worry about my
carpal tunnel
syndrome or anything.
(piano music)
- Good!
- [Mike] Good boy,
you can be trained!
♪ Really love your peaches ♪
♪ Wanna shake your tree-- ♪
(phone ringing)
Damn, you ruined it again!
- Hello?
Oh hello, Gordon.
- I've been trying to get Jeff.
Sonya's here.
How's it coming?
- Wonderful.
You wanna hear something?
- You bet.
I'll turn on the speakerphone.
I want Sonya to hear it.
(piano music)
- [Mary] Fine, listen to this!
♪ I wish I had a
castle in the sky ♪
♪ Way up where the
bluebirds fly ♪
♪ A castle with
the sky full of-- ♪
- [Mike] Oh crap, we're
opening tomorrow too.
♪ Skies for windows, clouds for
rugs, a rainbow for a door ♪
- [Tom] Jeff, we're having
some trouble hearing.
Hold on.
I'm trying to get the
speakerphone working, Jeff.
Hey, wait a minute.
Don't start playing
the song until I get
the speakerphone working.
How the hell's this thing?
Start the song.
From the beginning.
We can't, speakerphone.
- Woo!
- [Mike] Hey, hey, leave
room for the Holy Ghost.
- Woo-hoo!
(romantic music)
Welcome to Shakey's!
Elton John was here.
- [Tom] This would be
a good companion film
with "Eraserhead."
- I love it!
Such rhythm, such spirit!
Such good fortune!
- That's it, kids.
Bring it in, Jeff, and
go on your honeymoon.
- [Tom] Walter
Cronkite approves.
(romantic music)
- [Mike] Jacket.
Condoms.
Lingerie for me and you.
- Let's go to your mother's!
- [Mike] The baby will lock up.
- [Tom] Okay, Jeff, we're
all set on this end,
go right ahead.
- [Mike] Ah, the monks for
St. Gregory work on their next
big chart-busting hit.
- I'll just order the hit.
- Chief, this is Wilbur.
Mission accomplished.
I'll be right up.
Bye.
- Now I can do the decorating.
- [Tom] Now I'll see what Tad
and Bryce are up to. (giggles)
- I'm losing his
pattern, captain.
- [Mike] The following
scene contains
graphic sexual content.
- What the hell was
that about, anyway?
(slamming shut in sequence)
(childish piano music)
- No, no!
(childish piano
music in higher key)
No, that roundly sucks.
(vocalizing along
to piano music)
♪ Sword and magic helmet-- ♪
Hey! (giggles)
Woo!
- Waaaaaah!
(crashing)
♪ I wish I had a
pretty purple phone ♪
♪ To match my
purple Gypsy color ♪
Whoa!
Say, thanks, wow.
- Hi.
- Oh, let's see.
♪ I wish I had a lovely phone ♪
♪ With combined Kenner
Easy Bake Oven ♪
- All right, okay.
Oh geez it's heavy,
oh man it's heavy.
- Oh, oh!
Hey, hey.
- It might still be in there.
- I think I turned my shorts.
♪ I wish I had a
Princess Moon Mountain ♪
♪ On half of an ocelot ♪
- What's an ocelot?
- C'mere, c'mon, get up there.
Oww!
(chainsaw buzzing)
- Hey, that looks, wow.
- Phew.
♪ I wish I had one
of those things ♪
♪ With a thing on it
and they were cheap ♪
♪ And one of friends in
college had with me ♪
(phone ringing)
Hey, whoa, this is fantastic.
- It's for you.
- Okay, whoa.
♪ Hello, hello ♪
♪ Hello hello hello ♪
♪ I don't know why you
say goodbye, I say hello ♪
♪ And if you say goodbye
I'll sock you in the eye ♪
♪ Then line you up
against the wall ♪
♪ And pop goes the weasel ♪
♪ And if you say goodbye,
I'll sock you in the eye ♪
♪ Then line you up
against the wall ♪
♪ And pop goes the weasel ♪
- Brought to you by
our Phone Council,
reminding you to
decorate with phones!
- Phones!
(upbeat music)
- [Tom] Night Mother Move
Soccer of the Iguana.
Sausage, blood sausage.
- [Mike] Oh well.
- Music by Ray Manzarek.
- [Mike] Scott
McCloud, space angel.
- [Crow] Ah, you
lost your trailer.
Ah nevermind.
- [Mike] Hey, Ed Nelson of Ed
Nelson Plumbing and Heating.
Free hotdogs for the kids.
- [Tom] From a sentence
by Gene Corman.
- NASA simulation.
- [Mike] Help, the
conductor's having a seizure!
- Dick Courier: when Dick
absolutely, positively
has to be there overnight.
- [Tom] Isn't this
the "Polevetsian Dance
No. 2" by Borodin?
- [Mike] Yeah.
This band stinks.
This has been
thoroughly Corman-ized.
- Yuck.
You know, I don't know
that much about space
but it seems like they're
just wandering around.
- [Tom] Wow, it is a Gene
Corman signature movie.
- Ah, there's going
to be some turbulence
seeing as we have one wing.
- [Mike] From the sun and
fun capital of the world!
- [Crow] And now, our story.
- [Pilot] This is X100 to
Goldenrod, X100 to Goldenrod.
Do you read me?
Over.
- When I fly the real
one, I'll have more stuff.
- [Pilot] Starboard
is set on instruments,
knot is set on instruments.
- [Mike] This thing
won't boot up!
- I repeat, 90,000 feet.
Approaching critical velocity.
- [Tom] And I have a
bulbous growth on my nose.
- Something's wrong,
I'm falling too fast.
- So I'll just pull everything.
- Oh my God, I'm in trouble.
The jets won't break my speed.
- [Mike] I am
switching to blend.
- [Pilot] I'm releasing
the parachute.
- [Tom] If it returns,
I'll love it forever.
If it doesn't, then it was
never mine to begin with.
- I'm being severely backlit!
- [Pilot] There's no
drag and I'm getting
too close to the Earth.
- [Mike] I'm afraid of intimacy.
- [Tom] Whoa, I knew I was
lactose intolerant but...
- My pizza!
- [Pilot] There's nothing
more I can do now.
- [Mike] Party tape, woo!
- [Pilot] 10 miles
northeast to your location.
In case recorder's
damaged, get this.
- [Tom] Help!
(riffers coughing)
- [Pilot] Weight ratio 187.
Thrust 220 tons.
- [Tom] Pants: totally filled.
- [Mike] It starts.
- Rut Patrol, in color!
- [Mike] Boy, Houston
doesn't waste much time.
Got a guy in a Jeep
right out there.
- [Tom] Someone's burning
leaves and NASA is there.
- [Mike] It's a Lands' End ad.
- Available in loaden,
camel, stone, pant and twerp.
- [Tom] Mark Trail!
- [Mike] With GORE-TEX.
- I told you, no hot plates.
- [Tom] I couldn't get the Jaws
of Life so I brought Cindy.
She's really strong.
- [Mike] NASA's
highly sophisticated
firefighting techniques.
- Anyone in here need OFF!?
- [Mike] Cindy, clear the shot.
- [Tom] Did I hit the ocean?
- [Mike] Ah, no, it's
Spooner, Wisconsin, Gary.
- Hi, I'm Bill Proxmire,
I'm running for Senate.
- [Mike] His pop spilled.
- [Tom] Ah, he's a mess,
you got a moist towelette?
- Should've sent up a dog first.
- I'll...
- [Mike] Have a
sandwich, if that's okay.
- I'll tell the others.
- [Mike] Am I a other?
- S'cuse me, could you
move your entrails aside?
- [Mike] Vanna
Bourke-White on the scene.
- [Tom] Oh I'm fine,
don't worry about me.
- Am I having a feeling?
Do I need a perm?
- [Mike] Their space
program ain't so good.
- Ah, Breaker One-niner
for the Big Booty,
we got a SPAM in the
can and we'll catch ya
on the Big Bounce 'Round, over.
- Goldenrod Baker
to Goldenrod Abel.
- [Tom] He's not that
alive anymore, over.
- Goldenrod Baker
to Goldenrod Abel.
- [Mike] The rest of
NASA rushes to the scene.
- Goldenrod Baker
to Goldenrod Abel.
- Nuh-nuh-nuh nrrn nrrn nrrn.
- Goldenrod Baker
to Goldenrod Abel.
- [Tom] Hold on, we're switching
all power to the radio.
- [Mike] If it's
Gary I'm not here.
- Did you find it?
- Came down about three
miles east of Walker's Pass.
Area 116 and 117 on your map.
- How bad is he?
- You ever see stroganoff?
- [Dave] He fought
it all the way.
- [Dr. Wyman] You're certain?
- No respiration, no
heartbeat, no pulse.
Came down pretty hard.
The rocket unit's
still in one piece
and most of the controls.
- [Tom] Thank God!
- [Dave] Everything
else is scattered around
for about half a mile.
- [Mike] Including Bob.
- Tell Donna to cover
the entire area.
Canaveral will want all the
visual data we can give them.
Oh and don't move anything
'til we get there.
- Goldenrod Baker out.
- Look, a frog!
- Terribly sorry, Julie.
- [Tom] But you're going
to have to scooch over.
- I understand how you feel.
- [Mike] I lost a husband once.
- But we can't let it interfere
with the work we have to do.
We both knew it was
a calculated risk.
- So, Arby's everyone?
- I'll be all right, doctor.
- [Mike] Oh I'm fine
too, don't even ask.
- Let's get going.
- [Tom] This was back when NASA
was family owned and operated.
- Before this decade is
out, we will put a man
in a pick-up truck and bring
him safely to Mendocino County.
- [Tom] It's great how they
can run the space program
and then sell corn from
their flat bed truck.
- Dave.
- [Mike] What should
I do with my gum?
- Look at the
composition of this mud.
- Don't play, honey.
- Dr. Wyman wants
you to get full
coverage on the entire area.
- [Tom] I don't wanna
take a dumb picture.
- This is your first project
under Dr. Wyman, wasn't it?
- [Mike] Oh, I've
been under him before.
- Yeah.
I helped design the jettison
unit; it didn't work.
- Then remember that other
thing that didn't work?
- On a project like
this, there's always
a margin for error.
You expect it.
- [Tom] Especially when
it's you working on it.
- Then when it
comes, you'll find
you really didn't
expect it after all.
- [Mike] Who knew
we needed fuel?
- You think Julie expected it?
With his engagement
ring on her finger?
- Not sure what I meant by that.
- John Corcoran
was the first man
to be sent up in a satellite
and ejected back to Earth.
Only he was supposed
to come back alive.
- [Tom] Stupid jerk.
- Let's check the rest of it.
- Look, Dave.
Don't blame yourself.
- The answer lies
in this wreckage.
Let's recheck the crash pattern.
- [Mike] Noo, let's just go.
- No, no Steve, not now!
Eh hehehe.
- [Tom] Hey, the
rug is escaping.
- [Mike] Well, this is like
Night of the Ground Squirrel.
- [Tom] Hello! (whistling)
Puppies? (whistling)
- Oh no, Patrick Stewart
fell into quicksand.
- [Tom] And action.
- Hi, NASA!
Ha ha ha, oh.
- Well, that's funny.
- What's that?
- This rip was smaller
when we first got here.
With the stress of settling
into the ground, it widened?
- [Tom] Yes.
- How could that be?
The entire hull is made
of magneridium alloy.
I'd like to examine the
body before we bring it out.
- [Mike] I'll need to be nude.
- Watch you don't
cut yourself, doctor.
- [Tom] Be vewy careful
with my hat, uh huh huh uh.
- That's a nice little Quonset
hut spaceship he's got.
- [Mike] Honey, your
mother's worried.
Why aren't you
getting up for school?
- [Tom] Okay, let's see,
righty tighty, lefty loosey.
- [Mike] Did he have a
skull when we sent him up?
- [Tom] Well, at least they
can strip him for parts.
- Dr. Benson, come here quickly.
Bring my bag.
- Dad never asks me
for his bag at home.
- [Mike] Oh man,
she's gettin' it.
- [Tom] Thanks, I
need my tennis shoes.
- Boy this is cool, this is
just like "Alien Autopsy."
- [Mike] Oh yeah,
yeah, that's cool.
- I want you to see this.
- [Mike] Look how dead he is.
- [Tom] Yeah, it's probably
an outpatient thing.
- How long did you
say he's been dead?
- Oh let's see, ever
since I've known him?
- It's been at least three
hours since the crash.
- Over three hours and
no sign of body rigidity.
- [Tom] Well that's nothing new.
- No skin discoloration.
Temperature feels normal.
- [Mike] Well, let's give
him more time to die.
- No dilation whatsoever.
- Cause of death must be
due to an internal rupture.
- He should've worn a cup.
- I've never seen an
internally damaged body
with no sign of rigor
mortis after so long.
- [Mike] And I love it.
- Let's get him back to the lab
so we can continue
the examination.
- [Tom] Is your freezer empty?
- [Mike] There's a layer
of fudge on this capsule.
- It's a girl.
- [Tom] Look at this, mealworms.
I could raise these and
make good money at home.
- Help Dr. Wyman.
He wants to take
John back to the lab.
- [Tom] Sphagnum peat moss?!
- Dave.
- That's really gross.
- Get a blanket.
- [Mike] Yep, I'll
drive this back to NASA.
(upbeat music)
- It all started at a 500 watt
radio station in
Fresno, California.
- [Mike] Please, no terrorists.
♪ This area ♪
♪ Restricted area ♪
♪ Duh dum bum bum bah ♪
♪ Trespassers are
shot on sight ♪
♪ By order of the government ♪
- NASA's fruit truck
makes a delivery.
- [Mike] I have to
question whether
this is really a
government operation.
- Well, we had to snap him
in two like a frozen dog
to get him out of the space
capsule, but I think you'll--
- [Tom] Ow.
- [Mike] How's this work?
- Hello Everglade, hello
Everglade, this is Goldenrod.
This is Goldenrod.
How do you receive, over?
- [Mike] I'm putting a
burrito in the microwave,
you guys want anything?
- Are they receiving us?
- That's not the question.
Are we transmitting?
They don't receive anything
from us, they won't try
and reach us until the
frequency check at nine o'clock.
- Hmm, what should
I wear to a funeral?
- [Tom] Anyone want sandwiches?
I'm heading into town.
- [Mike] Huh, he's
a little low on air.
(giggles)
- By all medical standards,
this man is dead.
- So just like before, then.
- No heartbeat, no respiration.
- [Tom] Never seen
a man so dead.
- Yet his tissues
refuse to dissipate.
- [Mike] Well I'm
gonna make 'em.
- Is it possible he'd be in
a kind of catatonic state?
Could he still be alive?
- No, get out.
- That is a form
of hypometabolism.
- That's impossible.
- [Tom] Maybe he's dead.
- His heart is stopped;
there's no circulation.
You know as well as I do
that when this process stops,
the brain starts to
deteriorate almost at once.
Within a matter of
three minutes, it dies.
- [Mike] It's like
he's dead or something.
- Hello Everglade,
hello Everglade.
This is Goldenrod,
this is Goldenrod.
How do you receive, over?
- I'm a photographer, he he he.
- Maybe after this
long a radio silence,
they'll switch over to
an emergency channel.
- [Tom] I mean,
that's what I'd do.
- I've already tried that.
How about the Air Force?
- [Mike] Maybe they're home.
- Hello, Air Force
emergency, this
is special C-Q-D
Goldenrod station.
How do you receive, over?
- Air Force is so stuck up.
(riffer mimicking
radio whistling)
- I couldn't receive a spot
weather report on this thing.
- Are you sure
it's not your set?
- No, I've already
checked everything.
Will you go out and ask Steve
to come in here a minute?
- Sure.
- [Tom] Okay, STEVEEEE!
- [Mike] I could've done that.
- Hello Everglade,
hello Everglade.
This is Goldenrod,
this is Goldenrod.
Do you receive, over?
- [Tom] Well, he's still dead.
- [Julie] Nothing, doctor.
- Hello, handsome.
- [Julie] Doctor!
- [Mike] He's got
senior wenis disease.
- [Tom] Hey look,
jelly comes out.
- What is it?
- Not a lesion.
More like something
had been forced through
the tissue at a high pressure.
(riffer growling)
- Have you guys seen my brush?
- Steve.
- [Tom] Yes?
- [Mike] Yes?
- Yes?
- The radio still won't work.
Dave wants to see you.
- Okay.
I bet they're going
nuts at the Cape.
- [Tom] Yeah, they're
partiers, woo.
- Just make it work, Steve.
We're gonna need assistance.
- [Mike] I'll keep
fiddling with the corpse.
- [Tom] I found a Chiclet.
- Hey, she walked up twice.
- [Mike] Hi, have
you been helped?
- [Tom] Hey, c'mere and help
me shake the candy machine.
- What's the trouble?
- I can't transmit across
the room with this thing.
- Hm, gold star, huh?
- Sounds like a
magnetic disturbance.
- Yeah, could be the power
lines fouled up outside.
What's happening in there?
- [Tom] Ah, big spring dance.
- I don't know.
Somehow we've gotta get
through to the Cape.
- Five hours (mumbles)
I bet half the brass in
the state of Florida's
having a heart attack.
- I hope not.
Enough people find
out about this,
we'll have everybody out here.
- [Mike] Where is up here?
- I'll check the tower.
You stay here and keep trying
to get through, will ya?
- All right, taking you up to
news time with the Chucker.
- Look, if you pick up
anything, give me a yell, huh?
- All right.
- [Tom] Sure.
Ram it, clown.
- [Mike] He's getting deader.
- Blood pressure 120 over 80.
Normal for a living man.
- That's impossible, doctor,
you must've made a mistake.
- But doctor, I
checked it twice.
- But you're a girl
doctor, doctor.
- This man does have
normal pressure.
- [Mike] It's as if he's dead.
- That's impossible.
- [Tom] It's inconceivable!
- Take a blood sample, I'll
let the radiation go at it.
- [Mike] Hah, ladder
that same evening, ha ha.
- [Crow] Don't.
- [Mike] Well, you do the--
- [Crow] Well, I--
Mr. Fawlty, she's-a
crazy, she hit me!
- [Tom] Blood Beast?
- [Mike] Okay,
there, I fixed it.
- [Tom] Hey you guys,
ladder's loose again.
- Goldenrod to Everglade,
Goldenrod to Everglade,
come in Everglade, over.
- [Crow] Restricted
changing area.
- [Mike] I wanna find
our picnic stuff.
- Goldenrod to Everglade,
come in Everglade.
This is an emergency.
- [Tom] You see?
- [Mike] Everglade
you dick weeds.
- This is a stupid
space program.
I'm gonna go work for my
uncle's space program.
(riffer grunting)
- [Mike] The
outhouse is connected
to the main breaker at NASA.
(giggling)
- Now you stay in
there, Mr. Power.
- [Tom] Very interesting.
- Steve?
- [Mike] Not everybody is Steve.
- [Crow] Steve,
Steve, cut it out!
Dah dah dah dow, dah dah
dah dow, pew pew, dah dow!
- [Tom] And the
Steves are there.
(screaming)
- Steve One, you go that
way, Steve Two, come with me.
- [Mike] This has Steve
written all over it.
- [Dr. Wyman] Are you okay?
- [Dave] Yeah.
- Uh-oh, undercupping.
- [Dr. Wyman] What happened?
- Something hit me.
It was big like a bear.
- [Tom] Was it a bear?
- [Dave] It came
out of the darkness,
it was headed for the lab.
I know I put a couple of shots
in it before I went down.
- Wounded animal that
large isn't good.
How well are we armed?
- Well, besides his pistols,
we've got a couple of rifles.
- I think it headed toward
the back of the building.
- Dave.
- [Crow] Who's Dave?
- Are you sure you're all right?
- Yeah, yeah, it
just clipped me.
(clattering)
- Steve!
- [Mike] C'mon, we're
late for biology.
- Dun duh duh dun dun,
duh duh dun, duh dun.
- [Dr. Wyman] Wait a minute!
- [Tom] I'll get the costumes.
- You guys be the Yankees
and we'll be the Nazis.
- [Mike] Mm, neat, did
you get this at Pier 1?
- [Tom] Now, that and a 10k
really lights up the place.
(theremin trilling)
- [Mike] Steve?
Steve?
- [Tom] Shh, don't wake up
Dad, he's in a really bad mood.
- [Dr. Wyman] Get the windows.
Tell 'em to get
the other lanterns.
- [Tom] Let's talk fast
for the rest of the movie.
- [Steve] Did it get to him?
- [Dr. Wyman] No.
- What do you think it was?
- This didn't come off any bear.
Bring the light
over here, will you?
- [Tom] Ugh, that's
mine, my back has been
flaking off like crazy.
- No fur, no blood.
- No disco, no foolin' around.
- Very much like leather.
- [Mike] Can I go home?
- Is the power out completely?
- [Tom] No, just partly.
Of course it's out completely!
- Yes, it is.
- You have any idea
what caused it?
- Could be break in
the cable at the dam or
a short circuit in
one of the transoms.
- [Tom] A squirrel.
- Dave, are you sure the
building was thoroughly checked?
Are the wiring and
the fuses all right?
- Oh, I know
everything thoroughly.
I checked everything.
Ah, I'll check again.
- Maybe they shouldn't
have launched
a rocket while the
dryer was running.
- [Tom] Yep.
- Nothing's wrong here.
Like I said, it's probably
the disturbance up at the dam.
- Well, Steve needs some
help boarding the window.
- [Mike] Get Steve on it.
- [Tom] There, all set in
case the birds attack us.
- Well, at least
we won't freeze.
- Unless it gets really cold.
- A place like this would
be equipped with heating.
- Up until a few months ago,
this was a radar
monitoring station.
- [Mike] Before that
it was a carwash.
- The ultrasensitive
instruments respond better
to the cooler atmosphere.
Systolic was 140.
- [Tom] So just lay off.
- I'll have a blood sample
for you in just a few minutes.
- [Mike] Make it two.
- I think it'll take
an hour to realize
we're incommunicado
and send aid.
Security operation
as tight as this,
may be another 12 hours.
Could mean we could
be here another day.
- [Crow] Ouch,
everything's so little.
Oh, tiny fried eggs.
- [Tom] Who order
theirs sunny-side up?
- Doctor, doctor!
- [Tom] Oh wait, nevermind.
- I've never seen
anything quite like it.
a saltine up close.
(riffers laughing)
- [Julie] Notice the way
it's fighting the others.
- [Tom] My God, I'm pregnant.
(upbeat music)
- [Tom] One, two, three, go.
(laughing and grunting)
- Ahem.
H-Hem.
- Uncle, uncle, uncle!
- [Tom] Uncle, uncle, uncle.
(nervous laughing)
- Oh hi, Mrs. Forrester.
You're looking nice today.
- Yeah right, look kids,
my Clayton has something
he wants to say to you.
Don't you, Clayton?
- I do?
- Yes you do young man.
Now you come right
here front and center
and you tell your little
friends what you did.
- Mother, don't talk
to the experiment.
You'll taint the data.
- You come here and apologize.
- Mother, apologize for what?
What did I do?
- Don't take that tone with me.
I think you know.
The high school incident?
- Oh, I'm sure I have no idea
what you're talking about.
- Clayton!
- Mother!
- Clay.
- Oh, was it the time
I ate the bag of wool?
- No, the bad thing.
- Oh, hah, I peed in
Bryan Furlong's locker.
- No.
- I puked Coco Puffs
and hot chocolate
into Kevin McConnell's jacket.
- No!
- Is it poop related?
- Clayton, you know very well
what it is and I think you
will feel better if you
just admit it and apologize.
- Mother, make it stop.
- Clayton Deborah
Susan Forrester.
- All right Mom, all
right c'mon, you and me!
C'mon, we will dance.
C'mon, you wanna piece of me?
Huh, huh?
C'mon.
Huh.
(gun clicking)
(cartoonish gun shot)
Ah, oh!
Ahhhh, gee!
(cartoonish gun shot)
Oh, nice shooting Mother!
Oh, Mother, blood.
- Aren't you hooligans
due back into the theater?
(panicked shouting)
(whizzing open in sequence)
- Seven hours and his
blood is still alive.
- [Crow] Steve, you can still
lead a full and productive life.
- [Tom] Just reminded of when
my turtle died, that's all.
- [Mike] (sighs) What I'm about
to say might sound strange
but I think we should
eat this corpse.
(chuckling)
- One of us will have to drive
to the nearest telephone
and call the Cape.
Every minute counts.
- What is it?
- [Tom] There's a cartoon
in the microscope.
- I've seen amoebic dominance
of a cell structure before
but this is completely
out of proportions.
- What are they?
What do they mean?
- Well, normal blood
has two basic cells.
- [Mike] Duh.
- The red carry oxygen
and the white fight infection.
But this blood has three.
The third cell, that big one.
- [Mike] Remember that one,
the big one, he had the hair.
- Well, that's completely
foreign to any blood structure.
- [Crow] God I'm in a funk.
- If that bacteriod is
contagious, then we've
all been exposed.
- [Crow] Bacteriod?
- I doubt if it's communicable.
- We better get to the
nearest town, fast.
- [Crow] Okay, bye.
- I imagine that'll
be Desert City.
- But that's over 30 miles.
Isn't there anything closer?
- [Mike] There's gotta
be a Pizza Hut nearby.
- There's nothing on the map.
- [Crow] I'm gonna kill myself.
- Steve, call the
Cape from Desert City.
Get in touch with Dr. Zimmerman.
Don't go into detail;
just tell him to get here
as quickly as he can.
- What about equipment?
- [Mike] Yeah, get some
of that too, I suppose.
- Well, we'll need
a new power supply.
A refrigerated truck or an
ambulance to transport the body.
Oh and--
- [Crow] Get yourself
something nice.
- Tell 'em to request
priority clearance
directly to Walter Reed
Hospital in Washington.
- Right.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
- [Tom] Oh, and snag some
brews and a couple sandwiches
and a thing of wax worms.
- Keep checking the
blood pressure, doctor.
- The last count
was 140 over 80.
- [Crow] What a
selfish thing to say.
- That's all we can do is--
- [Crow] I'm gonna
go walk in front of a bus.
What's the point of all of this?
- [Tom] Look at
those little guys go.
Wow.
- [Mike] Could you turn
the light off in the hall?
- Oh, so like a blood beast can
dismantle a distributor cap?
- [Mike] Time to
dance, blood beast.
- [Crow] I bet it's those nuns
from "The Sound of Music."
- [Tom] Steve!
- [Mike] Steve?
- Any luck with the Jeep?
- I can't figure it out.
The coils in both the truck
and the Jeep are burned out.
- [Tom] That's the
most insulting thing
you've ever said to me.
- [Crow] I suppose
I should apologize.
Yowww!
Oh oh, ho ho.
- [Tom] Anyway, thanks
for listening. I...
- [Mike] Look, we missed
the first half of "Friends"?
- They're both stopped.
- Everything's goin'
wrong in this movie!
- [Mike] He's an odd little man.
- [Tom] I just developed
a picture, everyone!
- [Crow] If you're looking for
that one thing, Barb moved it.
- [Mike] Steve, Steve and I
have something to tell you.
- [Dr. Wyman] Take a look.
- [Mike] This was in my tuna.
- We're in a
magnetic forcefield.
- [Julie] A what?
- A net of static
electricity is surrounding
the entire area.
- That's why our power's dead.
- Well, we're not
going anywhere tonight.
The truck and the Jeep are
burned out electrically.
- What would cause
a thing like that?
- [Tom] God hates us.
- There's a very
powerful magnetic
source somewhere nearby.
It's reversing all
positive electrical power.
- You sly boots.
- Dr. Wyman, how close is
the satellite compartment?
- [Crow] Who cares?
- Two, maybe three miles.
- [Dave] Just thinking, is it
possible that the compartment
could be bombarded with
electron particles?
- Could be, it's
happened before.
Some of the earlier (mumbles)
- [Crow] Snarf farm?
- When the missiles
came back to Earth,
they were pretty
heavily magnetized.
- There's a mountain range
between us and the compartment.
- Yeah, well, that doesn't seem
to be any logic
behind any of this.
- Here's something to
complicate things even more.
- I took these upside down!
- The shot I took when Dave
and I first got out there.
Look at it closely.
- [Mike] Now, lick it.
- Dave, you remember I
mentioned the strange mud?
- Yes.
- Well, this was
the last shot taken.
Most of the mud has disappeared
and the opening is larger.
- Yes, I remember
that when we took
John out of the compartment.
But at the time it
didn't seem important.
- Someone or something
must've been there.
- [Mike] Saw a huge
blood sucking alien
but I didn't think it
was important either.
- Ahh, I'm gonna go kill
myself again. I don't...
- [Tom] Steve?
Steve!
- [Mike] Hey, anyone
remember Pringles?
- There's an explanation and
a good one for all of this.
- Elves!
- There must be.
- [Mike] Hold on, I
guess there's not.
- Some of the things
that have occurred today
are without precedent.
- [Tom] Ah, just ignore me.
- There's a man in there
alive that should be dead,
something that's
never happened before.
- [Mike] Well, once, but he
had the wind at his back.
- We never sent a man so
far into space before.
- So little food and no air.
- Well, we're all
tired, disappointed.
- Stupid.
- Under a terrible strain.
- [Mike] I feel good.
- After this long,
the Cape has probably
contacted the Pentagon.
It's just a matter of time.
- What if they
can't get through?
The magnetic force
field works both ways.
- [Tom] Okay, so I'm wrong.
- Well, in the morning one
of us will have to hike
down and meet them.
As a precautionary measure
I suggest we all stay
in this room tonight.
- [Crow] I'll lay on Sharon.
- Dave and I will take
turns watching the corpse.
All right.
- [Tom] Hey, you're taller
than last year, honey.
- Condescend, condescend.
- Julie.
(crying)
- I'm sorry, doctor.
I just can't hold
it back any longer.
- [Mike] I have to overact.
- I wish there was
something I could say.
- I guess I just said that.
- I'll listen if you like.
♪ Girl, you'll be a woman soon ♪
- It's bad enough
losing someone you love.
But this, the unknown,
being held here.
- [Tom] Yeeeugh!
- All exiled.
- [Mike] You know, my
gown opens from the rear.
(sobbing)
- [Tom] Say, hello.
- Julie.
He alone stood on the
threshold of our future.
- [Mike] And he peed
it down his leg.
- From what happened
to him today,
we may learn more
than we've ever known.
- We've learned not to send
Pollacks into space, phew.
- Maybe I should've judged this.
- [Tom] There'll
be other Steves.
- He may be gone.
- [Mike] Oh mamma
that is so sweet.
- But is he dead?
- Look, let's not make a
federal case outta this.
- [Tom] You know, the
listening thing went over
like a lead balloon.
- [Dr. Wyman] Scientists,
the more we learn,
the more we realize
there is to learn.
- [Mike] Scientists?
- [Dr. Wyman] Life itself
is the greatest miracle.
Well, when we get him to
the hospital tomorrow,
maybe we'll know.
- [Mike] Ugh, all my adenoids.
(sniffles)
- [Crow] Could you
massage my front now?
- Good night, doctor.
- Good night, Julie.
- [Tom] Those three
little ties in the back,
slips right off.
- [Mike] Well, I just
needed to talk to somebody.
I've been a little down.
Thanks a lot.
- You need one of these, huh?
- [Mike] Oh, here
comes the nutty part.
(farting sound)
- [Tom] It's an easy one.
- [Mike] Now, come on.
- 'Twas brillig, and
the slithy toves of,
oh, what the hell am I thinking?
- [Mike] Martha Graham!
- [Tom] Who put my
sweater in the dryer?
(old-fashioned horror music)
(creaking)
- [Tom] Sorry!
- [Mike] Wait, there's one
last piece of carrot cake.
I'm gonna have it, he he he.
- Hey!
- What is it?
- [Mike] Did you put
the blood beast out?
- I hear something in there.
- [Tom] Be vewy quiet, we're
hunting blood beast, he he he.
- The light's out.
- [Mike] Loin chop?
No, I don't think so.
Huh?
- Ew, the patient
has blown a gasket.
- [Tom] Hi, we're looking
for an honest man?
- Dr. Wyman.
- [Mike] Put some pants on.
- Half his head's gone.
- [Tom] Oh, that's
his hinder, Steve.
- Yep, it's the dismount
that always impales 'em.
- Dr. Wyman!
- [Mike] You march straight
down from there, mister.
- There's nothing you can do.
- [Tom] Unless you
know where his face is.
- [Mike] Another long
scene in here should help.
(giggling)
- [Steve] Must've
taken the body.
- Whatever it is, it works fast.
- [Crow] To provide
soothing relief.
- Let's take him down.
- [Tom] You said he could
stay up until New Years
and that means
Christmas is over.
- [Mike] I forgot to tell
him that Rhonda called.
- [Tom] Oh, oh God, I
slipped on his face.
- [Crow] Ew!
- [Mike] Oh, oh God.
(screaming)
- [Tom] Yeah, I get
that a lot, buh.
- Oh, I just blew all
over the operating room.
- [Mike] Well, welcome
back to the land
of the living, mister.
- Steve.
- [Tom] What, me
Steve or he Steve?
- Help him to the table.
- Let's shoot him back into
space and see what happens.
- [Mike] How 'bout hello, hi?
Anything?
- Johnny.
- Oh, Steve's name is Johnny!
- Johnny, you're all right.
- Julie, I don't know.
- [Mike] I dunno.
I think so.
- [Tom] Can I have
an Eskimo pie?
- Where's Dr. Wyman?
- [Mike] I hadn't
finished his head.
- What happened?
- Won't you tell
us what happened?
- Julie, what
happened to Dr. Wyman?
- He's dead.
- [Mike] Thank you, Julie.
- [Tom] Hey, wait up.
- Why're you staring at me?
You don't think that I had
anything to do with it?
- Johnny.
- [Mike] A.K.A. Steve.
- We're just as
confused as you are.
Did you see anything?
Was there anybody in the
room with you and Dr. Wyman?
- I don't know.
- I don't wanna hear
I don't know, mister.
- Last thing I remember--
♪ I was headed for the door ♪
- I was making my descent.
The jets didn't take hold.
When I finally released the
drag chute, it didn't hold.
I was too close to the ground.
- You crashed.
We brought you here.
- You're so full of it.
- You don't remember?
- I seemed to be floating,
in a warm, black mist.
- [Tom] Ah, we gave
you a pudding bath.
- Ohh, my head!
- [Mike] My achey, breaky head.
- My neck!
- [Crow] Have you seen it?
- Oh no, look at that.
- The same mark.
- [Mike] I told him
not to pick at that.
- [Tom] Oh, did that thing pop?
- Heuh huh huh, hey,
it's old pizza back.
- [Mike] See, I got a little
nutty with a wood chisel.
- What's this?
- [Tom] You think
I'm Steve, don't you?
- Tell me what's happening.
- Johnny, you don't understand.
We thought you were dead.
- And frankly, we're getting
pretty used to the idea.
- [Mike] Yeah, we
sold off your organs.
- Whaddya mean, dead?
- [Tom] Don't yell at us.
- When we pulled you
out of the compartment,
your body had completely
ceased to function.
- Whaddya mean, compartment?
- A hypometabolistic state?
- [Tom] No.
- [Mike] No.
- [John] Some type of
suspended animation?
- [Mike] No, no no
no, you were dead.
- [John] Brought on
by the contraction of
the mesenteric blood vessels?
- [Tom] That's so sad.
- That kind of terminology I'd
have expected from Dr.
Wyman, not from you.
- You wash your
mouth out with soap.
- Well, it seemed like
the natural diagnosis.
- From Dr. Wyman, yes.
- In some way I think Dr.
Wyman is influencing me.
I think he may be
a part of me now.
- [Mike] Can you be dead again?
- [Tom] I don't really
think that, ha ha ha.
- I don't understand!
You've got to help me.
Help me!
- This is unbelievable.
Things like this
just don't happen.
- [Crow] This is helping.
- [Tom] Thank you,
really, thank you.
- I'm not afraid.
I'm not afraid.
- [Mike] Afraid not am I.
- It didn't come
here to destroy.
- Johnny, try to tell us.
What didn't come
here to destroy us?
- No more questions,
more boobies.
- Is he all right?
- [Crow] Oh, this
one's not as nice.
- They're gone.
- [Crow] My bronies are gone.
- [Tom] I've got a
bassoon if we need one.
- What are you talking about?
- Come see for yourself.
- [Mike] Ya big, dumb,
dead guy, siddown.
(riffers vocalizing)
- Normal in every respect.
Four hours ago, it was populated
with alien, amorphic
cell structures.
- [Mike] They mean
to win Wimbledon.
- I think we should
see what I look
like under the fluoroscope.
- [Tom] Yeah, that'll
kill some time.
- [Mike] Put a shirt
on while you're at it.
- How will it work
with the power out?
- It operates on a
radium cathode tube.
- [Mike] Ohh.
- Wow, he's loaded
with shrimp, cool.
- The amorphic cell
structures have expanded to--
- [Mike] Jacksonville!
- They're using his body
for a breeding ground.
- You're not gonna
harm them, are you?
- What do you mean?
- [John] We don't even
know what they are.
- The one thing we
do know was that
they're alien to the human body.
- [Tom] Young man!
- Somehow they must've come down
with you in the compartment.
- [Mike] You're gross.
- [Julie] Only a few hours
ago they were microscopic.
We've got to do something.
- If you destroy them,
you'll destroy me.
♪ Steves don't preach,
I'm in trouble deep ♪
- [Mike] You know
what, I think I get
hush puppies and
coleslaw with these.
- You can't destroy them.
- [Crow] I'll take care of them.
- Why not?
- That's why not.
- [Crow] Kramer, I love him!
(screaming)
- [Mike] Barnie's
been in a fire.
♪ I love you ♪
♪ You burn me ♪
- Steve, don't shoot
him, I'll hurt you.
(gun shots)
Steve, don't shoot
him, I'll hurt you!
(screaming)
- [Tom] This is no way
to meet the in-laws.
(screaming)
- [Mike] Ah boy you know you
marry the whole family, huh?
- [Crow] Yeah.
- [Tom] That's true.
- Not the copier!
(screaming)
- [Tom] My resume
was in there, oh ho.
- [Mike] Hey look,
I'm really sorry,
I thought Johnny told
you I was dropping by.
- [Tom] Oh, oh boy.
You can't stop me from
seeing my children!
- Come back here you varmint.
- [Mike] You stupid
wall, stupid wall.
(fake sobbing)
Stupid, stupid wall.
(dramatic music)
- [Mike] C'mere
you little tramp.
When I think of the blood
beast's hands all over you...
- It's burnt but it
got away, didn't it?
- It didn't go very far.
- It's gone.
It was burnt pretty bad.
I think we oughta track it
down and make sure it's dead.
- No, let's wait for help.
We can't possibly combat
that thing by ourselves.
- Look, nobody's
gotten to us, no one
probably will until
it's destroyed.
- Why does it have to be killed?
- Don't you think he's cute?
- Why are we always
so quick to destroy?
It's an alien, it's
the first of its kind
to come to the Earth.
- John, you know what
it's done to you.
Breeding its young in your body.
You saw what it
did to Dr. Wyman.
Isn't that reason enough?
It has to be killed.
- I don't understand.
It didn't come in malice.
It could've killed all of you,
only it was me it was after.
- [Tom] And I loved
every minute of it.
- To nourish its young.
- [Mike] That's weird, Steve.
- All the more
reason to destroy it.
- Suppose it is still alive.
Bullets don't harm it.
- [Tom] I got it handled, Steve.
- But fire seems to.
What about a Very pistol,
engulfed in flames,
plus a delayed explosion?
- [Mike] Very pistol?
- It's better than a lantern.
- Very pistol?
- A flare gun, at a short
range, it'll chop down anything.
- There's some in the cabinet
in the hall, I'll get 'em.
- No, Dave, you can't!
Listen, you can't
kill a living creature
without giving it a
chance to justify itself.
Agh.
- [Crow] Ohh, sorry, hormones.
- Let's put him in there.
- [Tom] Ah yeah,
Grandma's old room.
- [Mike] Well, I'll
try to raise them
as if they're my
very own shrimp.
- Ah yeah just lay him
on the ironing board.
- [Tom] So, Julie,
guess he wasn't
getting enough at home, huh?
Julie?
- Can you give him
something to keep him quiet?
- Sodium amytal.
- Good.
- [Mike] Or you could
just turn on cartoons.
- We'll leave you
here to watch him.
Donna'll come with
us, we're gonna
need photographic coverage.
- Oh, this is going
right in my eye.
- Will that really keep
him out 'til we get back?
- I don't know.
Under normal circumstances,
this should render
him unconscious for
at least 12 hours.
- That's if he was
a normal person.
- [Tom] This is
no ordinary Steve.
- What you and he
were to each other
has no bearing on
what he is now, Julie.
- [Mike] Actually, it
was pretty lukewarm.
- I'm not worried.
He's not dangerous.
Not to me, anyway.
- 'Cept when the Packers lose.
- Well, we can't
take any chances.
That creature eludes
us and comes back here.
- [Tom] Look, I am
trying to shoot up.
- Or if he gives you a
bad time, you better know
how to use a Very pistol.
Believe me, Julie,
he's not the same man
you were engaged to.
- [Mike] Here's your
Frankenberry pistol.
- Thanks, let me have
one for Julie, would you?
- There you go,
that'll do you, bye.
- Now don't worry.
We run into any trouble,
we're not gonna be heroes.
- [Tom] Now, who's Roes?
- Pull the hammer back.
- [Crow] And blow my head off.
- Just be back as
soon as you can.
- [Mike] Nnnnope.
- [Tom] God, this
feels great in my hand,
I've got to kill something.
- Don't make any sudden
moves, honey bunch.
- [Mike] Steve, I
need to iron a blouse.
Could you sleep somewhere else?
- [Tom] You know, he's
really not showing that much.
(upbeat music)
♪ Edelweiss, Edelweiss ♪
- [Mike] Well, I can't
find the blood beast
but I see the beast
of Yucca Flats.
- Thank God this lot's a
lot healthier than I am.
- You know, I think
it's leading us
back to the compartment.
- [Tom] I hear a birdie.
- It looks that way.
- How long do you
think we've been out?
- Well, Tom came out last year
and then Steve was
gonna come out--
- Look, my watch
is running again.
- [Mike] Mine's not, ya fem.
- Mine too.
- That means that magnetic
field must be broken.
It must be dead.
- [Tom] So, what're
we all looking at?
- We better make certain.
- If we throw a shower for
Steve, can there be egg salad?
- [Mike] Look, a lupin.
- [Tom] Ah, blood beast
is doing his laundry, see?
- [Mike] Uh-huh.
- [Tom] Up there.
- Jordan said if I ever
got in trouble to come
back here to the
place by the crick.
- [Mike] Cliff has
Billie Idol hair.
- Blood beast! (whistling)
Blood beast! (whistling)
Buddy.
- [Tom] Oi, imagine
how much lower
we'd be if we were down there.
- [Mike] Are we camping?
Is this camping, you guys?
You know, I never went camping.
One time we went to North
Dakota when I was little
to visit Uncle
Ron, he had a horse
and it stepped on me.
I think it was a horse.
- If we do have a shower,
we could probably get stuff
that's green or
yellow 'cause even if
they are boys or girls
they can still use 'em.
And if aliens even have sex,
I don't think they have it.
'Cause what if they did?
- Well, it seems like the most
likely place for it to go.
- Yeah, I don't see anything.
Maybe it's on the inside.
- Yeah.
- Donna, you stay here
until we're sure it's safe.
Dave, you circle to the left
and I'll go to the right.
- 'Kay.
- [Tom] Mm, maybe I should've
gotten the purple blouse.
I don't know.
- [Mike] Stay Donna, stay
there completely alone.
That's best.
- I had a naughty
thought, hm hm hm hm.
(whimpering)
- [Mike] You know, a blood beast
can outrun a quarter horse
for the first 50 yards.
- Maybe if they
had a blood hound.
- [Tom] God, his
droppings are enormous.
- [Mike] Move 'em out.
- [Tom] I got skunked
on blood beast
but it's a great day
to be out in the woods.
♪ Doo doot doot doot doo doo ♪
♪ Toot toot toot toot toot too ♪
(gun shot)
- Ooh, the blood beast
is making jerk chicken.
(sniffing air)
Mmm!
- Nothing could possibly
live through that.
- [Mike] And we know
for sure it's in there.
- Look, it stopped again.
- Hey Steve!
- [Tom] No, stay
there, stay all alone.
- [Donna] I gotta
get some pictures
before there's
nothing left to shoot.
- [Mike] Sure, you can use it.
(screaming)
- [Crow] Sigmund the
Seamonster's got me!
- [Tom] How could he possibly?
He could live if
he's not in there.
- [Mike] Mannix!
Double Mannix!
- [Crow] Our plan
is going perfectly.
- [Mike] Hey mister
a little help.
Can we have our woman back?
- [Tom] Hey, good place
to get lucky under there.
- Oh baby I was misnamed.
I'm really the love beast.
- [Dave] Hold it!
He's gonna kill her!
- Fire over its head.
- [Mike] You think
I'm, oh I see.
Huh, huh.
I regret nothing!
- Are you hurt?
- No thanks, I just was.
- I don't think so.
It could've killed me.
But it didn't.
- Probably would've if
we hadn't chased it off.
Might've wound up like Wyman.
- [Tom] Bill Wyman?
- We better get back.
- [Tom] I panicked.
- Julie's all alone
and the monster may try
and contact Corcoran again.
- [Steve] Yeah, let's go.
- [Tom] Hey, it's one of
those guns that says bang.
♪ Janie got a gun ♪
(dramatic music)
- Oh, he is showin'.
- [Tom] Oh geez, oh no no,
I can see every contour,
oh my God, make it go away.
- [Mike] And God bless
Grandma and please don't
let the alien babies eat me
in my sleep, thank you, amen.
Howdy m'am.
- Don't be afraid, Julie.
- [Tom] Can I make you a shirt?
- I'm not gonna hurt you.
- [Mike] It's just
the way my pants fit.
- That wasn't meant for you.
That was for the creature
or whatever it is.
- You can call him the
creature, it doesn't offend him.
- Don't stare at me, Julie.
- [Tom] And don't
look at my area.
- [Julie] I'm sorry, John.
- [Mike] I'm sorry that you
look like Andrew McCarthy.
- If what you say is
true and I've been dead.
- Will I still get
calls from Citibank?
- I don't know what
this means for us.
But I haven't changed
in my feeling.
- [Tom] I need sexual healing.
- Julie, we're all
afraid of the unknown.
You don't understand
what's happened to me
and because there's
an unknown being,
we want to destroy it.
- [Tom] Unknown bean?
- But isn't it possible
that what's taking place
is for a purpose?
- Illogical positivist.
- Why not let the
creature have a chance
to tell us why it's here?
- But it broke in
and attacked us.
It killed Dr. Wyman.
It's done this to you.
- [Mike] He shrimped you.
- We had to do something.
Now the others have gone
to make sure it's dead.
- It's not dead.
And they won't be
able to find it.
- How do you know?
- [Tom] Stuff.
- Julie, I am the one who's
had the most contact with it.
- No duh.
- Something foreign
is inside me, alive.
- [Mike] I'm filled with scampi.
- If there was any cause for
fear, wouldn't I know it?
But I'm not afraid.
This creature is intelligent.
It wants something.
We've got to give it a chance
to communicate with us.
- [Tom] Here's your
Count Chocula pistol.
- [Mike] Did he nibble at
your neck like I used to?
Did he know all the
little things you like?
Oh God I don't wanna hear it.
- [Tom] Whoa, somebody
lose a toenail?
- [Mike] We're sending
you to stay with relatives
until this whole
thing blows over.
- I see the sedative
didn't work.
- My bodily reactions aren't
those of a normal person.
- [Crow] I'm Italian.
- What happened
to the creature?
- He got away.
- Then it's alive.
He told me it would be.
Somehow he knew.
- [Tom] He's a witch!
- He seems so sure
that it's not evil.
- This isn't a battle between
men and a non-reasoning being.
Can't you see it doesn't wanna
kill for the sake of killing?
It could've done
away with all of us
earlier if it wanted to.
- Until we discovered
its fear of fire.
- Listen--
- [Tom] (speaking gibberish)
- When you were out
checking the power lines
last night, all you had
with you was a pistol.
Which you fired at
it with no effect.
If it had been a wild
animal, it would've
tried to kill you
before moving on.
- [Tom] That mole.
- Can you account
for what happened to Dr. Wyman?
- He fell against
the coffee table.
- No, I can't.
But maybe it could if
we give it the chance.
- Why should we
give it a chance?
- [Tom] Sorry.
- It's already committed murder.
It's done I don't know what to
you and it's attacked Donna.
- [Mike] Donna
omitted for clarity.
- Look, if you were
in a strange place
and you were trying to
communicate with the inhabitants
but every time you tried,
they made a move against you,
the only way to
break through to them
would be to take a hostage.
Can't you see that's
what it's been doing?
It's been acting out of
fear and self-preservation.
It wants to communicate with
us but it doesn't know how.
We've got to give it a chance.
- What do you have in mind?
- [Tom] A sleepover, aha!
- It's obvious the
creature keeps coming back
to me because part of
it is inside of me.
- Part of him was
inside you, yeah.
- Why not let me lead us to it?
In the daylight, in the open.
- [Steve] Maybe
he's got something.
- [Mike] Yeah, Sea-Monkeys.
- When we were out
searching for the creature,
our watches started
running again.
Then when we encountered
it, they stopped.
On our way back here,
they became active again.
And now everything's dead.
- [Tom] You're the only one
interested in this, Steve.
- Now, it's my guess that
the magnetic disturbance
originated from two
different locations.
- [Tom] Hoo boy.
- One from the creature--
♪ And one more for the road ♪
- And then from you.
- It might be the only thing
that's keeping you alive.
- [Mike] Herbalife
is keeping him alive.
- If my life has been given
back to me, it's for a purpose.
Trust me and you'll learn why.
- If the creature isn't
what you believe it to be
and we're forced to
kill it, then we have no
indication of what
will happen to you.
- I know.
- [Tom] Let's review:
what're we talking about?
- That's why it's important
that the creature
make itself known
before we take any action.
- All right, but if we
follow Johnny's plan,
we still have to be prepared.
We have no way of knowing what
can happen to us out there.
- I felt a kick.
- Remember, we've agreed
to give the creature
every opportunity
to prove itself.
- In the morning we still
agree to follow Johnny's plan,
we'll get an early start.
- By that time maybe
help will arrive.
- Dave and I will stand guard.
The rest of you get as
much sleep as you can.
- Will it come
back here tonight?
- [Mike] Well, we
didn't have a date
but he stops by most evenings.
- I don't know.
- [Tom] Okay, and the plan is?
- So, why a trapeze?
- [Mike] I don't wanna know.
I'm gonna go get AliveWell
for my babies, all right?
- [Crow] At least this
is better than "Junior."
(chuckling)
(slamming shut in sequence)
- Hi, Mom, Dad, little red guy.
I have something to tell you.
I have lain with blood
beast and I am pregnant.
Don't believe me?
Here, look at the fluoroscope.
- Oh, sure.
- Fluoroscope?
- Five, oh my God!
- Please don't make this
any harder than it is.
We're in love and
you can't stop us.
He's going to work
at Stokely's 'til
the end of the summer
and then he's going
to move in with us.
- Gee Crow, they kinda look
like peel n' eat shrimp.
- Thank you.
- Do you need
a glass of water?
- Crow, how did
this happen anyway?
- Oh, me, a blood
beast, a bottle of wine.
- Would you like a pickle?
- You know, Crow, I don't
really believe you're pregnant.
- Mike, I'm crowning
right now as we speak.
- Ohh!
- All righty then, I'm pregnant,
could be complications.
Here, I've got a
list of demands.
- Oh, okay.
- Let's take a look here.
Complete bed rest with
comic books and videos.
Servo must clean my room
and I get all his food.
Hey Crow you're not pregnant.
You haven't even got a womb.
- And I think you're
supposed to give me
a baby shower right
about now, whaddya think?
- Crow, I mean, how would
you even have a baby?
Why don't you just admit
you're not pregnant?
- Okay okay, I'm not pregnant.
Hey everybody, I'm not pregnant!
Ah, that means I don't
get a big free ride.
Oh, my ankles are
swollen, my back hurts.
Carry me, I'm
pregnant, carry me.
Well, I want a cut of
the action too, dammit.
- Crow!
- Yeah well, who wouldn't
wanna be pregnant, huh?
Who wouldn't want to be a big
load on the rest of the world.
Hey everybody, I'm
queen of the world
because I'm pregnant
then the whole world
is supposed to bend over and
smooch your ever-widening ass.
- Crow, Crow, Crow.
- Geez, geez.
- Well when is it my turn?
When is it Crow T. Robot's turn?
(sobbing)
- We'll be right back.
You're fine.
- Oh no.
(upbeat music)
- [Crow] My water broke.
- [Tom] So anyway, I
trusted that Eagle Scout
and he let me down.
- Steve.
- [Mike] What is it, Steve?
- I'm a little worried
about Johnny's plan.
- So am I.
- Hard to trust a
guy not named Steve.
- I don't know if he's
responsible for his actions.
- [Tom] And he's puttin'
on too much weight.
- You think it might be a trap?
- If it is, this time we're
gonna be prepared, c'mon.
- [Mike] I think Johnny's
lying about the babies
and just wants the
alien to marry him.
- Bread and butter pickles?
- How 'bout a Molotov cocktail?
- [Mike] It's pretty
early, I mean.
- We fill it with
gasoline and then
use it as a hand grenade.
- That's the ticket.
- [Tom] A hanger nade?
- Look, we saturate the creature
and detonate it
with a Very pistol.
There's no way it
could escape that.
- [Tom] Yeah, nothing
could live through that.
- So, whaddya think?
- [Dave] How many bombs
are we gonna make?
- Well, between us, we oughta
be able to carry about six.
- [Mike] My God you are mad.
- What're we gonna
do with the girls?
- They come with us.
Better than leaving
them here unprotected.
- I can carry three.
- That's enough.
- Are we gonna tell Julie
and Donna about this?
- I think we better make sure
Johnny doesn't find out, huh?
- [Tom] Let's keep
it between us Steves.
- You ever see any
of these work before?
- [Mike] King Oscar fish balls?
- Yeah, in (mumbles) canal.
- [Tom] You bought a canal?
- When a tank was running
wild behind our lines.
We knew we couldn't any
much damage with our rifles
so playing kind of
a cat and mouse game
'til they knew they
could finish us off.
- God you paint a picture.
- Not far from where we
were there was a truck
overturned and I came down
to see what was happening.
Got the brilliant idea
to bring me some gasoline
and made up some of these.
- [Tom] All the guys
really liked 'em.
- A tank came by; we
smeared it but good.
- [Mike] Anyway, what
was your question?
- Pretty horrible to
see but it worked.
- Then there was
the year I fainted
before the talent contest.
- It'll be good for me to
get off of this mountain.
Even with these
cocktails, I'm not anxious
to tangle with that
creature again.
- None of us are but I don't
think we have any choice.
Came down in a satellite,
it's our responsibility.
Besides, better to stalk it
than have it come after us.
- [Tom] Yeah, that's
my dating policy.
- Yeah, you're probably right.
Even so I wish we could
wait for some help.
I just don't like
the idea of taking
Julie and Donna with us.
- Well, I don't either.
Then we don't know
when help will arrive.
We can't leave them alone.
- [Mike] Can't live without 'em.
- I don't think Dr. Wyman's
gonna need the chin-up bar.
- [Tom] So NASA has one
fully equipped hospital room.
- [Mike] Oh geez look
at this clown, c'mon.
Hey weirdo, hey freak,
how are the shrimps?
Weirdo freak boy.
- What are you doing here?
- What are you doing
with Dr. Wyman's body?
- Hey, I'm not into that.
- I couldn't sleep.
Well, I had to see
how he was killed.
Half his head gone,
it's horrible.
I don't expect you to trust me.
I don't even know that
I can trust myself.
- [Tom] Johnny, honey, hello?
- [Johnny] Please don't
treat me like a monster, I
haven't done anything wrong.
- John, it's not a
question of right or wrong.
Maybe you're not responsible
for your actions.
Whether you are or not, who
knows what you might do?
- [Mike] You're a woman in love.
- John, don't you realize
this unknown creature
is using your body
as a breeding ground?
We don't know what to expect.
- [Mike] He didn't use me,
I gave of myself freely.
- I can't deny
anything you've said.
- But you're a big fat liar.
- I do receive impulses
from the creature
but I know I have free will.
- [Tom] I can still
have a career.
- I know I can still
make my own decisions.
- Is it your own free
will or the creature's
that insists it's benevolent?
- [Mike] I'm sorry,
I was thinking about
the nursery, what?
- I'm not sure.
But I do know that we have to
give it a chance to explain.
- C'mon we're losing daylight.
I'll be in the car.
- Daylight will be here
in about three hours.
- Better get some rest.
- [Tom] Especially
you young lady,
you got a big day tomorrow.
- If it's all the same to you,
I'll stay here for a while.
- [Mike] Work on
my wedding dress.
- I'll get the bags.
- This guy is way over the edge.
- All right.
- You will give it
a chance to explain?
- We'll give it a chance.
- [Tom] Yeah, ka-blooey
okay, he he heh.
♪ He's once, twice, three
times a blood beast ♪
- Now the blood beast got mad
and spun shitties on the lawn.
- [Tom] Hey beast, honey,
are we still going bowling?
Bud?
- [Mike] Forgot their
Mrs. Butterworth's!
- (sniffing) The blood
beast has been drinking
and before our wedding night!
- [Tom] Ah, this
is where the movie
really swings into
high now, here we go.
- [Mike] Oh, nice shot.
- Oh if we could just,
well, there's something
in the way, I can't
figure out what it is.
- [Tom] Sorry guys,
I parked my Camaro
here somewhere, I dunno.
- It's a beautiful
day for a wedding
but why are they meeting
the priest out here?
- [Mike] Okay, bride's
side or blood beast side?
- The creature isn't far away.
There's some hills to
the north and a cave.
- [Tom] I'm seeing
the color orange
and someone is thinking
of the number 12.
- But he's never been
in this area before.
How does he know there's a cave?
- [Mike] I refuse
to answer that.
- [Tom] Ah by the way, anybody
lock up the space building?
- [Crow] Ah, I forgot.
- [Mike] I'm seeing
a wool pantsuit
and someone is hungry
for a frosted (mumbles)
- If the name says Corman,
there's gonna be walkin'.
- [Mike] Yep.
Oh there's a rock
with a big hill.
- [Tom] No no, you must
learn how to walk, Hobbes.
C'mon, with the knees.
- [Mike] With the knees, right.
- [Tom] Yes.
- [Mike] Ah, this is the
spot where blood beast
first told me he liked me.
- [Crow] Carry me.
- [Tom] Shut up.
- [Crow] Carry me!
- Carry me!
- [Tom] Shut up!
- [Mike] Ah, we have to flap
our wings and fly from here.
- [Tom] Ah, you know,
I haven't picked up any
impulses for about an hour now.
Maybe they weren't
really impulses.
Perhaps they were just notions.
Whoa, more undercupping.
- [Mike] Yep, I see it.
Yep, undercupping, undercupping.
Cup, cup.
- Everyone, I have an impulse
to wander like we're lost.
- [Mike] Oh, blood
beast scat, careful.
- [Tom] Maybe he was just
picking up a CB radio.
- You know, we could just
go to Midvale Mini Putt.
I'm supposed to meet
him there tonight.
- [Tom] Ow, my pants,
oh, both my pants.
- It's in there.
- [Tom] What?
Oh!
- Julie, Donna.
- Go check that out.
- Stay there.
There's nothing to fear.
- We're not going to take
any unnecessary chances.
- [Steve] The
girls'll wait here.
Okay, you lead the way.
- You're gonna give it a chance?
You're not gonna kill it?
You're not gonna kill it!
- [Tom] Elaine!
- [Donna] What happened?
- [Julie] Why did
you let him go?
- [Dave] We couldn't stop him.
- [Mike] Yeah, he thinks
he's Ida Lupino again.
He's all wigged out.
- Blood, sweetie,
they're gonna kill you.
- I brought them to you.
They don't understand.
I'm not sure I do.
How can I help you to
communicate with us?
- Now I am able to
speak by assimilation,
a form of photosynthesis,
I've been able
to incorporate certain of Dr.
Wyman's functional processes.
- [Mike] He turned
out to be very boring.
- Was Dr. Wyman's
death necessary?
- Through his sacrifice,
I can communicate,
understand your reasoning,
your motivations,
your way of life.
- Sweetheart.
- I will need your help.
Together we must
make them understand
that I have not
harmed you and we will
give them a better way of life.
- [Tom] Maybe not today
or tomorrow but soon
and for the rest of your life.
- [Mike] But anyway,
now I'm hidin' in here
'cause the dogs keep burying
me and digging me up.
- So anyway then I
transferred to junior college.
They had a better space
flight program over there.
- Look!
- [Tom] Here comes the bride.
- [John] Listen, please listen.
- [Beast] Do not be afraid.
(chuckling)
I am not here to harm you.
- [Mike] I just wanna kill you.
- It's too far away.
- [Steve] Let's move in.
- Ah, in our country it's
custom to throw gasoline
on the new couple, yeah.
(upbeat music)
(humming "Wedding March")
- Oh, the ceremony's about
to begin, I love weddings.
- [Tom] My nail's aren't dry.
- [Beast] Do not be afraid.
- That's Dr. Wyman's voice.
- It is his voice.
- But how?
- Yes, I am using
Dr. Wyman's voice.
- [Crow] I've got a little
problem with the reverb though.
- [Tom] I'm also using his
car and his apartment in town.
- [Beast] I have been
able to master the use
of many of his faculties.
With his voice, I am able
to communicate with you.
- [Julie] You killed him!
- He's not dead.
- [Crow] (mimicking
parrot squawking)
- [Steve] Not dead?
- [Beast] He has gained
something more than life
as you know it.
He is the first of your
kind to attain immortality.
- Immortality?
- [Mike] Wait, I mean death.
- I'm not interested in
that kind of immortality.
- I know you want to destroy me.
(riffers giggling)
But listen, please listen.
I only want to help you.
Millions of years ago,
my people inhabited
a planet such as yours.
We discovered the
ultimate power.
- [Tom] Radar!
- Just as you on
Earth are about to do.
- Get ready to make your move.
- We should've put this power
Earl to our own benefit.
- [Mike] Huh, wha?
- Instead, hatred,
greed and prejudice
caused us to misuse that power.
It brought about
our own destruction.
- Open target, now's our chance.
- But you can't
risk killing Johnny.
- Now wait.
- What harm is there
in hearing them out?
- [Beast] For a century, we
have been circling your Earth.
- [Mike] Okay.
- [Beast] Waiting for a means
to penetrate your atmosphere.
- [Crow] (giggling)
- [Beast] Your
projectile was the first
to present a means of entry.
Those before were
not retractible.
- [Mike] Man he goes on.
- [Beast] They
fell back to Earth.
I am the first.
- To come (mumbles) destruction?
- If what you say is true,
what are we to expect?
- You need me.
- [Crow] You need me, rawk!
- And I have come.
Through me, we will unite our
intellect within one body.
- [Mike] Ah man.
- This is insane.
- And how do you
plan to do that?
- Already it has begun.
- [Crow] Begun.
- Within the hour, the
first of our new generation
will be born.
- It's true.
- [Tom] I'm dilated to four.
- I can feel them inside.
- Get the cocktail sauce.
- You're imposing
your will on me.
- [Mike] Now now honey, not now.
- You're sacrificing
all of civilization
for the resurrection
of your own.
- [Tom] In the car, honey.
- I've been a fool.
- You've been a beautiful fool.
- The only way you could
be safe on your downfall
is by our sacrifice.
What your propose is
dominance, not salvation.
- [Mike] Oh please,
that's not the...
- Don't be governed by fear.
- Go ahead and kill me.
You've already said I'm dead.
A dead man with a brain and a
body kept alive artificially
to feed a generation
of monsters.
- That's not true.
- If you don't kill me, a new
civilization is inside of me.
- [Tom] A tiny civilization.
- That will destroy mankind
as we know it today.
The future of our
race is in you.
- They wrote their
own vows you know.
Ah, it's beautiful.
- You've got to kill me.
- We have to destroy it.
- [Mike] Yo, can do.
- John, run, get away from it!
- It's Operation Rescue.
- He will live on to
become a greater being
in future generations to come.
- [Crow] Generations.
- [Beast] Don't kill me.
- [Mike] Ya big dopes.
- [Beast] In destroying
me, you are destroying
your only hope for mankind.
- [Tom] You prude,
you let me go.
- [Mike] Yeah,
that's how it began.
(riffers chuckling)
- You've got to kill me!
- I'm having hard enough time.
- [Tom] Do I gotta
do everything myself?
(screaming)
- [Crow] Oww, oww, whoa,
eek, a ha ha, oh boy.
Ah, you can't
throw jars of rice!
- [Mike] My corduroys.
(gun shot)
- [Tom] Geez.
Hike!
- [Crow] He hates that rock.
Ah, save your own damn planet.
(singing "Wedding March" tune)
- [Tom] The St. Louis
Parrots mascot was burned
to death today.
- [Beast] You are not ready.
We will still save you.
In your quest for
self-destruction
you will send up
more satellites.
- [Crow] Satellites.
- [Beast] And we will be
there, waiting to come again.
- In the meantime
I'll just roast.
- [Mike] Bet it
smells like chicken.
- Mmm.
- [Tom] I wanted to be an aunt.
- Here I come too!
(triumphant music)
- [Mike] Whoa, phew.
- She got ahold of
a wet blood beast.
Whoa ho ho.
- [Tom] Now these Lutheran
weddings are so short.
- Should we split Johnny
open and scoop out the roe?
- [Mike] I think
that would be no.
- [Donna] Do you think we
made the right decision?
- [Mike] Well, there's good
arguments on both sides.
- John made the decision.
- Let's hope it
was the right one.
We'll probably never know.
- [Tom] Yep, just what
it is we'll never know,
we'll never know.
- Should we get Johnny or not?
- [Tom] Buy shrimp
where you work or play.
Okay, so, what was
the point again?
- [Mike] I don't...
(shutting in sequence)
- Yeah and that's another thing,
where do these babies
get off thinkin'
they're kings of the world?
Oh, I'm helpless,
feed me, change me.
Yeah, like okay, I
can't control my bodily
functions either,
Mike, so I guess you'll
just have to follow me
around and clean up my poop.
- Hey, Crow.
Can I just, can I read a letter?
- Yeah.
- Just this letter,
can I just read?
- Sure, sure.
Yeah go ahead it's fine,
it's just, you know.
Ah, go read, yeah.
- Okay, thanks.
This one's a nice one, it's
got a little picture with it.
Why don't you put
that picture up there?
- [Tom] Oh look at that.
- [Mike] Okay this
one's from Leah.
- [Tom] Hi Leah.
- [Mike] She says,
"Hi my name is Leah.
"I'm seven.
"I made a poppit
friend for Tom Servo."
She probably meant puppet--
- Oh do me a favor
and hand me that box-end wrench.
Wah, I can't, I'm a baby.
Well, look punk, if you
can't do me that one favor
that's just fine, fine.
- Hey Crow do you
need to just vent?
I mean, go ahead.
- No, no.
- C'mon, the floor is yours.
- Nah, nah.
It's just that.
Ah, go on with your letter.
- That was rough.
Let's see if we can
find another one then.
- Okay, all right, fine.
I got another nice letter here.
Again, put it on
still store, Cambot.
Thank you.
This one is from Lisa.
- [Tom] Lisa.
- She says "hey
guys, my name is Lisa
"and I'm 13.
"I always watch your later
show at night, my mom and I--"
- You know, frankly
it's about time
a few of the babies
out there started
pulling their own weight.
How many years has it
been, we've been pampering
and preening the little
pink larvae anyway, huh?
Yeah you know, the sick
thing is, I'm probably
gonna take a lot of
heat from baby lovers
just for saying the
things everyone else
wanted to say but
didn't have the guts.
Well, write in, write in to me.
Crow T. Robot, PO
Box Wah-wah-wah.
Huh, huh, huh.
♪ Hush little baby ♪
♪ Do not say a word ♪
- Oh that's not true, how
could you not love this baby?
- Mother, I'm not
a baby anymore.
- Hush, you are a
very naughty baby.
Go back to sleep little baby.
- I'm so glad my mother is here.
- What, baby?
- I mean, wah wah wah.
(sobbing)
(slow music)
- A wounded animal
that large isn't good.